<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fort Wayne's Best Real Estate Training</title>
    <description>David Brough, a top Real Estate Agent in Fort Wayne, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. His Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>https://realestatecareersinfortwayne.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://realestatecareersinfortwayne.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 13:39:09 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 13:39:09 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Negotiate Multiple Offer Situations</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/m4Ukq1Sf5P0?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seeing multiple buyers place bids on your client’s home can be exciting, but it also means you’ll have to start negotiating prices. There’s no need to worry, as there are ways to make this process simple and straightforward instead of stressful and disenchanting. &lt;strong&gt;Here’s what to do:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, have a conversation with your client. Together, you’ll need to proactively plan for a few things, such as times to communicate with other agents, the way you’re going to respond to multiple offers, and how you’re going to keep track of bids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=This is the way we do it; it keeps things professional and courteous while leaving nobody in the dark.%20https://realestatecareersinfortwayne.com/how-to-negotiate-multiple-offer-situations.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“This is the way we do it; it keeps things professional and courteous while leaving nobody in the dark.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, make sure potential buyers know to submit their best offer by a certain time you’ve chosen—this ensures everyone will have the opportunity to decide on a price. Once you’ve received the final prices and made a decision with your client, it’s time to make some calls to agents and buyers. You simply need to accept the offer, make a counter-offer (if you choose to do so), or explain that the seller chose to go with a different buyer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the way we do it; it keeps things professional and courteous while leaving nobody in the dark. In the end, the best offer wins, but the open communication we keep will ensure everyone leaves happy. Remember, these potential buyers are still looking for homes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to receive updates on new videos, please subscribe to our newsletter. If you have any questions or need some information, feel free to contact me and we can talk. I look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 14:42:51 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://realestatecareersinfortwayne.com/how-to-negotiate-multiple-offer-situations.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://realestatecareersinfortwayne.com/how-to-negotiate-multiple-offer-situations.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
